module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What job has Jane NOT held?', 
      a: 'Convenience Store', 
      b: 'Egg Gaherer',
      c: 'Car Mechanic',
      d: 'A Company President',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which famous marriage did Taylor\'s cousin break up?', 
      a: 'Puff Daddy & JLo', 
      b: 'Carson Daly & Tara Reid',
      c: 'Ashton Kutcher & Demi Moore',
      d: 'Jared Leto & Cameron Diaz',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What TV show did Tom Hanlon\'s former employer star in?', 
      a: 'America\'s Most Wanted', 
      b: 'Next',
      c: 'Room Raiders',
      d: 'Jerry Springer',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who did JLowe model golf stuff for?', 
      a: 'Academy', 
      b: 'Dick\'s Sporting Goods',
      c: 'Sports Authority',
      d: 'Canadian Tire',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Aaron\'s wife has written what type of book?', 
      a: 'Fiction', 
      b: 'Romance/Smut',
      c: 'Adventure',
      d: 'Young Adult',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Lynn has NOT broken this bone.', 
      a: 'Nose', 
      b: 'Humerus',
      c: 'Ankle',
      d: 'Tibula',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was Troy\'s Middle School extracurricular activity?', 
      a: 'Mariachi Band', 
      b: 'Woodworking',
      c: 'Ultimate Frisbee',
      d: 'Debate',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What character did Catherine play in Middle School theater?', 
      a: 'The Mad Hatter', 
      b: 'The White Rabbit',
      c: 'The Cheshire Cat',
      d: 'The Caterpillar',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who went to space camp at NASA?', 
      a: 'Elizadeath', 
      b: 'Joelle',
      c: 'Nick',
      d: 'Lauren',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following Clearheaders is 25% Korean?', 
      a: 'Lauren', 
      b: 'Taylor',
      c: 'Tyler',
      d: 'Colby',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};